forextime.com 2011-10-10

# Privacy & Refund Policy

  *  Just  
Beginning? 
  *  Becoming  
a client 
  *  Our trading  
terms 
  *  Trading  
platforms 
  *  Managed  
accounts 
  *  Become  
a partner 
  *  Deposits &  
withdrawals 
  *  Forex  
Analytics 
  *  About  
ForexTime 

### 1\. Obligations of the Company

The privacy of clients, both present and former, as well as other website visitors is a high priority. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") describes how the Company collects, uses and protects the personal information of the Client.

This Policy does not require the Client to provide any additional information beyond that which has already been furnished to the Company.

### 2\. Personal Data

When a Client opens a demo or live account, the Company needs to collect certain information from the Client (“Personal Data”) for business purposes. The Personal Data that is collected will help the Company provide products and services that more closely fit the Client's interests. Additionally, this information helps the Company improve the quality of its consulting.

**The Personal Data that is collected may include:**

  1. personal information provided on applications and other Company forms, such as name, address, date of birth, passport data and occupation;
  2. financial information: income, assets, investment experience;
  3. documents provided to confirm identity, such as passport, utility bills, and/or bank statements or company incorporation information;
  4. payment documents: money transfer orders, bank statements, bank card copies, etc.

### 3\. Use of Personal Data

The Company may use a Client's Personal Data for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. to confirm the Client's identity;
  2. to process trading and non-trading operations;
  3. to inform the Client about Company products or services that might be of interest;
  4. to provide other services that are relevant to the Client's business relationship with the Company; 
  5. to keep a correct database of the Client’s account data;
  6. to analyze statistical data to provide Clients with the most suitable products and services;

### 4\. Cookies

Cookies are small files which are sent by a web server to be stored on a visitor's browser which can then be read later by the server when the visitor returns to the site. The file is sent to the server as a "http-request" each time the page is opened. Cookies may be used on some pages of the Company's site to customize the visitor's web experience. The majority of web-browsers allow cookies to be blocked without denying the user access to the site.

Cookies are not used to determine the personal identity of anyone visiting the site.

### 5\. Third Parties

The Company has the right to convey the Client's Personal Data to associated or affiliated companies, agents or any other authorized organizations or persons ("Authorized Persons") for the sole purpose of processing the Client's trading and non-trading instructions.

The Company guarantees that all Authorized Persons will adhere to this Policy and take all necessary steps to protect the Client's Personal Data.

The Company may provide Personal Data to third parties who are not the Company's partners, agents or affiliates only when requested by representatives of legal or administrative authorities.

### 6\. Use of Information

By registering an account with the Company, the Client consents to ForexTime collecting, maintaining, using and disclosing their Personal Data in accordance with this Policy.

### 7\. Security & Protection

ForexTime takes security issues very seriously and takes all reasonable steps, including maintaining strict security standards and procedures and using leading security technologies to protect the Client's Personal Data.

To make a deposit with a credit or debit card, the Client must fill out a form through a processing center's website. The data are then transferred to the Company through a secure connection and cannot be used by unauthorized parties. 

### 8\. Credit and Debit Card Refund Policy

In exceptional cases, ForexTime may refund payments made by credit or debit card. In this case, the funds will be refunded to the card that was used for the deposit.

### 9\. Contacts

Should you have any questions about this Policy do not hesitate to contact us: [info@forextime.com](mailto:info@forextime.com).

Risk Disclaimer: Trading with leverage is a high-risk activity. Your losses may potentially exceed your initial deposit. Before you start trading,  
you should completely understand the risks involved with the currency market and be aware of your level of experience in trading.

Registration number: [3274608](http://www.business.govt.nz/companies/app/ui/pages/companies/3274608?backurl=%2Fcompanies%2Fapp%2Fui%2Fpages%2Fcompanies%2Fsearch%3Fmode%3Dstandard%26type%3Dentities%26q%3Dforex%2520time) Registration number for financial services provider: [FSP111064](http://www.business.govt.nz/fsp/app/ui/fsp/version/searchSummaryCompanyFSP/FSP111064/1.do)

18 Stanley Street, Parnell, Auckland, 1010, New Zealand ForexTime NZ Limited

© 2011 ForexTime
